giftease.com 2014-11-23

# Privacy Policy | Giftease

**Giftease values the privacy of your personal information. We do not sell, or otherwise share your personally identifiable information with any third parties, except as may be necessary to provide the services which you have requested for, or for promoting a safe and improved experience on the Website, in accordance with this policy.**

**Please note that giftease.com does not capture or store your Payment Card details (i.e. credit/debit card number, expiration date, CVV etc.). When you make a purchase using your card, all required transaction details are captured on the payment gateway’s secured payment page, and are securely transmitted to your card issuer for obtaining an authorization decision. At no time during the purchase process or thereafter does Giftease have access to, or store, your complete card account information.**

Giftease maintains the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices.

Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

By using this Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Website.

By using the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use.

**1\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information and other Information**

When you use our Website, we collect and store your personal information which is provided by you from time to time. This information enables us to provide services and features that better meet your needs, and to customize our Website to make your experience safer and easier.

In general, you can browse the Website anonymously without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Website.

Apart from the personal information you provide by entering this on the Website, we may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on our Website. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Website or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Website or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Website to help analyse our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie".

We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Website and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session. The cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply (an example of this is when transact as a guest or add items to shopping bag). A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive.

Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

If you choose to buy on the Website, we collect personal information, including billing address, shipping address, contact numbers, email IDs, which are required by us to provide the services.

If you choose to post messages on our message boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback, or if you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law.

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, etc.) from you when you set up a free account with us, or provide your email ID to enable us to send you updates, or in the course of placing an order. While you can browse some sections of our Website without being a registered member or having an account with us, certain activities (such as placing an order) do require registration. We do use your contact information to send you updates as well as offers based on your previous orders and your interests.

**2\. Use of Personal /Profile Data / Your Information**

We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to address your queries and complaints, resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information. We use this data to tailor your experience at our Website, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in and to display content according to your preferences.

In our efforts to continually improve your experience on the Website, as well as to improve our services, we collect and analyse demographic, profile and behaviour data about our users' activity on our Website. **  
**

**3\. Sharing of personal information**

We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court  
orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.

We and our affiliates will share / sell some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity, or re-organization, amalgamation, restructuring of business. Should such a transaction occur, that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

**4\. Links to Other Websites**

Our Website links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Giftease is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

**5\. Security Precautions on Giftease.com**

Our Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

Although we will endeavor to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this website, you agree that Giftease will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

**6\. Opting In / Opting Out**

We provide all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account.

If you want to remove your contact information from all Giftease.com lists and newsletters, please visit  **My subscriptions” in the “My Account” section of the website, after you sign in.**

**7\. Advertisements on Giftease.com**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email  
address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**8\. Your Consent**

By using the Website and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Website in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to Your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**9\. Grievance Officer**

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below:

Mr. Vivek Mathur

Giftease Technologies India Pvt. Ltd.

Trade Centre, 401/2 & 403,  4th Floor, North Main Road, Koregaon Park, Pune – 411001

Phone: +91- (0)20 26153001

Email: [complainces@giftease.com](mailto:complainces@giftease.com)

Time: Mon – Fri (10:00 – 19:00)

**10\. Questions?**

Questions regarding this policy statement should be directed to the following address: [complainces@giftease.com](mailto:complainces@giftease.com)
